export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      " Do familiar surroundings sometimes seem strange, confusing, threatening or unreal to you?",

    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "no",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Have you heard unusual sounds like banging, clicking, hissing, clapping or ringing in your ears?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      " Do things that you see appear different from the way they usually do",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "no",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Have you had experiences with telepathy, psychic forces, or fortune telling?",

    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      " Have you felt that you are not in control of your own ideas or thoughts?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      " Do you have difficulty getting your point across, because you ramble or go off the track a lot when you talk?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Do you have strong feelings or beliefs about being unusually gifted or talented in some way?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "no",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      " Do you feel that other people are watching you or talking about you?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Do you sometimes get strange feelings on or just beneath your skin, like bugs crawling?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "yes",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Do you sometimes feel suddenly distracted by distant sounds that you are not normally aware of?",
    options: ["yes", "no"],

    correct: "no",
  },
];
